Part One: Moisturizer
To mitigate the effect of damage to the skin,
apply moisturizer twice a day,
once in the morning and once at night
to all areas of the neck- front and back,
the skin surrounding the mouth, the face,
and the upper portions of the chest above  your collarbone.
What this cream does is create a film
over your skin that acts like armor.
This armor prevents further skin dermatitis from accumulating.
The only time to not apply moisturizer is right before your treatment.
It ensures that the head and neck mask that
you wear during treatment remains clean.
You can apply moisturizer before your treatment
if it is well before your appointment,
and you can apply moisturizer
immediately after treatment.